<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Symmetrical OS News Feed</title>
		<item>
			<title>Before I forget...</title>
			<description>Symmetrical OS is almost ready! Also, here. Have an image. I think.&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="https://win98icons.alexmeub.com/icons/png/internet_connection_wiz-4.png"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>2023-10-21 00:49 UTC</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">si6</guid>
			<author>LeWolfYT</author>
		</item><item><title>Oh no, I forgot my password!</title><description>The installer is almost done. In fact so close that it would be possible to release it now! However, you can't log in to the new system. We have tried all sorts of methods of setting the user's password but no matter what we do, it will not work.</description><pubDate>2023-10-23 20:12:56 UTC</pubDate><guid>6168d27e-cf80-21f5-5bda-57dd019f</guid><author>SidGames5</author></item>
		<item>
			<title>Sid, I'm Disappointed In You (not really)</title>
			<description>You know, you could have asked me and I would have helped you with the dependencies.&lt;span style="visibility: hidden;"&gt;hey you, the inspect element guys. don't tell anybody. i'm hiding here in the code&lt;/span&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>2023-10-21 00:49 UTC</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">other2</guid>
			<author>LeWolfYT</author>
		</item>
		<item><title>Dependency hell</title><description>Oh python. The project leader, LeWolfYT, wrote the installer in python. One of the problems with python is dependencies. I mostly write in haxe which bundles the dependencies inside the program. Python does not. This means I have to figure out which dependencies are already included with python and add them to the ISO package list.</description><pubDate>2023-10-19 20:59:27 UTC</pubDate><guid>de86c367-dae2-0f16-6ee1-052c6502</guid><author>SidGames5</author></item>
		<description>Symmetrical OS News Feed</description><item><title>First ISO is almost working</title><description>The new new installer written in python is complete! We have begun VM testing and will soon begin hardware testing. Once all of that is done, it will be released to the public as the first ISO of Symmetrical OS.</description><pubDate>2023-10-17 00:00:55 UTC</pubDate><guid>c4c2e448-f192-8ed8-0a2b-02b76dc8</guid><author>SidGames5</author></item>
		<item>
			<title>Symmetrical OS Installer Development Update #5 - So close</title>
			<description>Symmetrical OS will be available soon... if I have enough motivation.</description>
			<pubDate>2023-10-13 12:18 UTC</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">si5</guid>
			<author>LeWolfYT</author>
		</item>
		<item><title>We are making a file manager!</title><description>We have just started development on a new file manager. Eventually this will replace Thunar included with XFCE4.</description><pubDate>2023-10-10 21:33:33 UTC</pubDate><guid>82ba0f5f-fe7f-98ee-e28a-79f46867</guid><author>SidGames5</author></item><item><title>First release delay</title><description>We originally planned for the first ISO to be available on October 1st. It will probably not be available until late October or early November.</description><pubDate>2023-10-05 11:20:00 UTC</pubDate><guid>3a9c0d46-b065-591c-926f-5b847430</guid><author>SidGames5</author></item>
		
		<item>
			<title>New news writer</title>
			<description>For a long time we have been manually writing the XML document to add new
				items to the news feed. We finally have a dedicated tool for writing new news
				articles!</description>
			<pubDate>2023-10-05 01:19:56 UTC</pubDate>
			<guid>21433c31-92b3-7e72-ddfa-8df6b814</guid>
			<author>SidGames5</author>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>News viewer will now show times in local time zone.</title>
			<description>The news viewer on the website's home page will now show the time of the
				post in your local time zone. Previously it would display in UTC.</description>
			<pubDate>2023-10-05 00:02 UTC</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">e5c5cd13-783a-4aea-b16d-b7b2fab011b9</guid>
			<author>SidGames5</author>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Symmetrical OS Development Update</title>
			<description>Our update utility is complete! We are in the process of testing the app.
				Once that is all done it will be ready to ship in the first version of Symmetrical
				OS.</description>
			<pubDate>2023-10-04 12:18 UTC</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">99c55374-1a09-4326-84af-608f21df21ec</guid>
			<author>SidGames5</author>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Symmetrical OS Installer Development Update #4 - TK</title>
			<description>I have a love-hate relationship with Tkinter. On one hand, it's simple and
				works well, but on the other hand, it's also been a giant pain.</description>
			<pubDate>2023-09-29 00:54 UTC</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">si4</guid>
			<author>LeWolfYT</author>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Core repository is finished!</title>
			<description>Escam's core repository now has all of the packages from the Arch Linux
				core repository. You will not be able to use these packages for a while because it's
				gonna take a bit of time to add everything the the database file.</description>
			<pubDate>2023-09-28 20:37 UTC</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">rp1</guid>
			<author>SidGames5</author>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Escam is almost ready!</title>
			<description>Our package manager, escam, is almost ready for release! In terms of
				features, everything is complete. There are just a couple bugs we need to work out.
				We will not be using escam as the main package manager in SymmOS until the entire
				Arch Linux core and extra repositories are converted to escam-compatible
				repositories.</description>
			<pubDate>2023-09-28 13:40 UTC</pubDate>
			<author>SidGames5</author>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">esc1</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Symmetrical OS Installer Development Update #3 - Whoops!</title>
			<description>We've been having some issues with the installer, but we're making
				progress! Mainly, we're rewriting it in Python. Stay cool!</description>
			<pubDate>2023-09-28 11:18 UTC</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">si3</guid>
			<author>LeWolfYT</author>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Symmetrical OS Installer Development Update #2</title>
			<description>The installer ISO is almost done! There are some issues here and there that
				need to be fixed before the release.</description>
			<pubDate>2023-09-20 01:57 UTC</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">si2</guid>
			<author>SidGames5</author>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Symmetrical OS Installer Development Update #1</title>
			<description>Development has begun on the installer! The first ISO should be
				downloadable very soon.</description>
			<pubDate>2023-09-17 20:05 UTC</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">si1</guid>
			<author>SidGames5</author>
		</item>
	</channel>

</rss>
